karmasandhan.com 2014-03-30

# West Bengal and Central Government Jobs and Recruitment News: Privacy policy.

##  Privacy policy. 

At www.karmasandhan.com, we give extreme importance to privacy of our visitors. We do not do anything hidden without knowledge of our visitors because it’s your right to know how we treat your privacy and so we have clearly outlines the types of information we ([www.karmasandan.com/](http://www.karmasandan.com/)) received and collect and also how it is used. If you want more information, feel free to write us anytime at: info@karmasandhan.com  

**Information collected on voluntary basis:**  
We, [www.karmasandhan.com](http://www.karmasandhan.com/), collect personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website on a voluntary basis. Voluntary basis collected information may include: Name, E-mail address and telephone number. You provide us this information only when you choose subscribes our Newsletter or contact us through our embedded ‘Contact-us’ form for any queries. We use this information of yours only to respond your queries. We do not provide your information to any third parties.  
Recently the "Contact Us" form on our page, which appeared inside an i-frame, is provided us by Kontactr. You can view their privacy policy to know more on how they maintain visitor's privacy from this link- <http://kontactr.com/privacy>  

**Information collected through Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
www.karmasandhan.com does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

**Information collected through Log Files:**  
Like many other Web sites, we (www.karmasandhan.com) make use of log files. With this log files we simply used to analysis how visitors arrives and exit.  The information in log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
For such purposes, we recently use tools provided to us by:  

  * StatCounter.
  * Google Analytics

To know how StatCounter and Google Analytics works, how they maintain privacy and how you can avoid their cookies & choose opt-out, you can visit their respective web address:-   
For Statcounter: <http://statcounter.com/how_it_works.html>  
For Google Analytics: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>  

**Uses of DoubleClick DART Cookie:**  
To serve ads on [www.karmasandhan.com](http://www.karmasandhan.com/), Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies.  
DoubleClick DART cookies helps Google to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.karmasandhan.com and other websites on Internet.   
Visitors/Users may anytime opt out of the use of DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this web address:- <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>   

We, www.karmasandhan.com, have some advertising partners who may use cookies and web beacons on our website. Recently our Advertising partner includes:

  * Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.karmasandhan.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
We, [www.karmasandhan.com](http://www.karmasandhan.com/), have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

For more detailed information as well as how to opt out of certain practices, you should consult the respective privacy policies of these third party ads servers.  
www.karmasandhan.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

You can also choose to disable cookies with the help of the options available on your browser.
